

# MILOŠ PETROVIĆ (23)

## FRONT END DEVELOPER

## ABOUT

Experienced Web developer with 3+ years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing interactive websites. Innovative use of technology and SEO to drive traffic and engage users. Able to complete projects efficiently and satisfy customers with attractive, user-friendly and responsive websites.

## LANGUAGES

Serbian (Native)

English (Fluent)

Germany (A2)

## SKILLS

HTML/CSS

Bootstrap / Tailwind

VueJS / ReactJS

NativeScript / JavaScript

Laravel (PHP) / SQL

WordPress / OctoberCMS

Search Engine Optimization

Photoshop / Illustrator

### CONTACT

Belgrade, Serbia +381 69 505 909 9 milosptr@hotmail.com www.milosptr.dev

## **EDUCATION**

2012-2016 • Grammar school in Zaječar

Information technologies

2016-2018

Faculty of Mathematics - University of Belgrade

Information technologies and computer science

### EXPERIENCE

2014-2015

Graphic designer & PR member

Union of secondary School students of Serbia

(NGO)

2015-pres

CEO & Web developer & Designer

AS Media - Marketing Agency

2015-2016

WordPress developer & Marketing member

Union of secondary School students of Serbia

(NGO)

2017-2017

jan-mar

WordPress developer / designer

Gafner Media - Switzerland

2017-2018

Front End Developer & Team Leader

eTech 360 (United States)

2018-2019

Front End Developer

Jungo digital solutions

2019-pres

Full Stack Developer & App Developer

Morph Networks

#### CERTIFICATES

aug 2020

SQL for Data Analysis

Udemy